Prince of Ning
Его Высочество принц Нинь
The family head has a message
Глава рода велел передать
Chancellor Chen's meaning is
И что же имеет в виду министр Чэнь
The family head's meaning is
Его слова
In matters
Если дело
Either don't do it
не делать не делай
Or
но если делать
Do it completely
делай до конца
His meaning is
Он имеет в виду
Let me think about it
Дай мне время подумать
Your Highness
Ваше Высочество
Delay will cause trouble
Если промедлить всё может измениться
How dare you
Дерзость
Since when
С каких это пор
Has Chancellor Chen been making decisions for me?
министр Чэнь решает за меня
I wouldn't dare
Не смею
This subordinate was presumptuous
Простите я погорячился
Didn't understand clearly
не разобрался
Spoke wrongly
и сказал лишнее
Second son
Братец
Our father didn't have you publicly tried
Отец не велел судить тебя публично
But had me interrogate you
а поручил это мне
What does that mean?
Ты понимаешь что это значит
You should understand in your heart
Ты и сам всё понимаешь
Since Chu Huan is willing to step forward
Раз Чу Хуань взял всё на себя
I can use him to fulfill my duty
мне есть чем отчитаться
Second brother
Братец
As long as you admit to poor management
Тебе нужно только признать
And negligence that harmed the state
что ты недосмотрел за подчинёнными
You can leave here
и ты выйдешь отсюда
And live freely as a prince
чтобы жить свободно как князь
As for Chu Huan
А насчёт Чу Хуаня
I can delay his execution
я могу оттянуть его казнь
When I become emperor in the future
Когда стану императором
I'll ensure he doesn't die
сохраню ему жизнь
What do you say?
Что скажешь
Second brother
Брат
Think of your princess
Подумай о своей принцессе
Can you bear to let her follow you
Ты готов обречь её
And ruin her life like this?
на погибель вместе с тобой
Second son
Братец
If you let go now
Если ты сейчас отступишь
We can still be brothers
мы останемся братьями